<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Octavian Hasna</title><link>https://www.hasna.ro/</link><description>Recent content on Octavian Hasna</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.hasna.ro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FunDictionary</title><link>https://www.hasna.ro/fundictionary/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hasna.ro/fundictionary/</guid><description>FunDictionary is an application that helps you find words in English dictionaries, play Hangman, Pheasant or Wordle games and much more.</description></item><item><title>DexOffline</title><link>https://www.hasna.ro/dexoffline/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hasna.ro/dexoffline/</guid><description>DexOffline is an application that helps you find words in DEX (the Romanian language dictionary) without being online, play Hangman, Pheasant or Wordle games and much more.</description></item><item><title>Privacy policy</title><link>https://www.hasna.ro/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hasna.ro/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Last Updated: Apr 13, 2022
This privacy policy describes how Octavian Hasna (&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rdquo;) and 3rd parties services (both &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;) collect, use and share personal information of consumer users of the website (&amp;ldquo;site&amp;rdquo;) and of the following apps (&amp;ldquo;products&amp;rdquo;):
DexOffline for Windows DexOffline Plus for Windows DexOffline for Android DexOffline Plus for Android DexOffline for macOS/iOS DexOffline Plus for macOS/iOS FunDictionary for Android FunDictionary Plus for Android FunDictionary for macOS/iOS FunDictionary Plus for macOS/iOS What we collect We get information about you in a range of ways.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://www.hasna.ro/projects/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hasna.ro/projects/</guid><description>A list with my publised apps, libraries and contest problems.</description></item><item><title>Publications</title><link>https://www.hasna.ro/publications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hasna.ro/publications/</guid><description>2018 Octavian Lucian Hasna &amp;amp; Rodica Potolea. Analysing a Periodical and Multi-dimensional Time Series. In proceedings of the International Conference on Mining Intelligence and Knowledge Exploration (MIKE) (pp. 268-278). Cluj-Napoca, Romania. link
2017 Octavian Lucian Hasna &amp;amp; Rodica Potolea. Robust feature extraction from noisy ECG for atrial fibrillation detection. Computing in Cardiology (CinC). Rennes, France. link
Octavian Lucian Hasna &amp;amp; Rodica Potolea. Time series - A taxonomy based survey. In proceedings of the Intelligent Computer Communication and Processing (ICCP) (pp.</description></item><item><title>Research</title><link>https://www.hasna.ro/research/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hasna.ro/research/</guid><description>My thesis goal is to extract patterns and knowledge from sensor data in order to drive improvements in the way customers use a given product. In this context, the fields of interest are:
Time Series Analysis, code Recommendation Systems Sentiment Analysis I am part of the Knowledge Engineering Research Group. My current focus is on overcoming source signal dependence in time series analysis.</description></item></channel></rss>